He's the one she loves to hate.
The Hating Game is a drama, comedy, romance film directed by Peter Hutchings.
Resolving to achieve professional success without compromising her ethics, Lucy embarks on a ruthless game of one-upmanship
against cold and efficient nemesis Joshua, a rivalry that is complicated by her growing attraction to him.
Lucy Hutton, played by Lucy Hale.
Joshua Templeman, played by Austin Stowell.
Bexley, played by Corbin Bernsen.
Helen, played by Sakina Jaffrey.
Danny, played by Damon Daunno.
Julie, played by Yasha Jackson.
The Hating Game is a 2021 American romantic comedy
film directed by Peter Hutchings.
It is based on the novel of the same name by Sally Thorne, and
stars Lucy Hale and Austin Stowell in the lead roles.
The film was released in theaters and video on demand on
December 10, 2021, by Vertical Entertainment.
It received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of new york city, based on novel or
book, rivalry, love-hate relationship, nemesis.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.